I think I already have a good idea what
this is going to be we're dealing with
some factorials usually you want to
reduce each of them in terms of the
smallest factorial so I'm going to
rewrite this 70 factorial as 70 times 69
times 68 factorial and then we'll bring
down the 68 factorial and the 69
factorial we can rewrite as 69 times 68
factorial so now we have a bunch of 68
factorials let's bring down the
numerator but on bottom I want to factor
out the 68 factorial 68 factorial times
what gives us 68 factorial that's 1. 68
factorial times what gives us 69 68
factorial that's 69. 1 plus 69 is equal
to 70. the 70s cancel and the 68
factorials cancel and that leaves us
with 69. let's use this to put it in a
box how exciting